<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>how to take care of a bonsai tree on JapanBonsai</title>
    <link>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/tags/how-to-take-care-of-a-bonsai-tree/</link>
    <description>Recent content in how to take care of a bonsai tree on JapanBonsai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/tags/how-to-take-care-of-a-bonsai-tree/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About basic bonsai styles</title>
      <link>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/basicbonsaistyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/basicbonsaistyle/</guid>
      <description>Bonsai, as a Japanese art form, is more regulated than itís Chinese counterpart, the penjing. Bonsai attempts to achieve the ideal tree, while penjing attempts to reproduce nature. This is why perfect styling exists in bonsai if you obey the ërulesí, while penjing leave you free to your creation. As a result these are the basic styles :
Broom (Hokidachi or Hoki-zukuri) A very harmonious style, this form has branches that develop at a certain height, forming an upside broom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GENERAl APPROACH TO BONSAI by John Y Naka</title>
      <link>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/genaral_approach_to_bonsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/genaral_approach_to_bonsai/</guid>
      <description>This step-by-step pictorial is designed to guide beginners through the mechanical process of cutting, shaping and transplanting fairly simple bonsai material for the first time. It makes the assumption that the reader has already done some research and has a basic understanding of the fundamental shaping concepts used in the art of bonsai such as:
  Select hardy plants. Conifers are mostly used. (specially juniper which is very good .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating A Bonsai For The First Time.</title>
      <link>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/biginnerbasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://japanbonsaigarden.com/posts/posts/biginnerbasics/</guid>
      <description>This step-by-step pictorial is designed to guide beginners through the mechanical process of cutting, shaping and transplanting fairly simple bonsai material for the first time. It makes the assumption that the reader has already done some research and has a basic understanding of the fundamental shaping concepts used in the art of bonsai such as:
  Triangulation and asymmetrical composition. Primary, secondary and tertiary branch identification and placement. Selection of primary viewing angle based on trunk movement and rootage .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
